

MACIEJ LICHOŃ

WEB DEVELOPER

+48 510 120 436

maciek.lichon@gmail.com

Links:







Based in Kraków, Poland

PROFILE

Frontend developer with a unique professional journey. I began my career in analytical roles, accumulating over 3 years of corporate experience. Seeking a change, I transitioned into the IT industry by completing a 9-month web development bootcamp, where I gained a strong foundation in the MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js) stack. In my current role, I specialize in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and TypeScript, crafting engaging user interfaces and web experiences that meet today's industry standards.

LANGUAGES

Polish - native

English - bilingual proficiency

EDUCATION

Kodilla

Web Developer Plus 2022

Politechnika Krakowska / Cracow University of Technology

- Power Engineering, Engineer's degree 2016
- Renewable Energy Engineering, Master's degree 2017

EXPERIENCE

MARCH 2023 -PRESENT Gecko Dynamics • Kraków, Poland Markup Developer

HTML, CSS, JS, React, TypeScript

- Working with the design team; designing and implementing user interface
- Cooperating with the marketing team; developing landing pages for marketing purposes
- Maintaining and updating internal websites
- Implementing reliable integrations with external services and applications (API)
- Developing HTML emails
- Working independently on external projects
- Taking part in technical decision-making

MAY 2022 -FEB 2023 IBM • Kraków, Poland Tax Equalization Process Lead

- Coordinating daily work of the team
- · Working closely with other stakeholders
- Conducting trainings for new employees
- Managing escalations and process flow
- Identifying gaps in processes and implementing new solutions
- · Acting as an SME

MARCH 2021 -MAY 2022 IBM • Kraków, Poland Sales Bonus Analyst

- Serving as the primary point of contact for sales reps worldwide
- Administering data in SAP Commissions
- Analyzing inputs and identifying inconsistent data
- Cooperating with other stakeholders
- Preparing ad-hoc bonus calculation analysis and reports

SEP 2019 -FEB 2021 AON • Kraków, Poland Online Benefits Administrator

- Managing and administrating benefits for multi-international clients
- Processing and analyzing sensitive data
- Tracking data and managing issues
- Testing new and existing online platforms
- Cooperating with Configuration, Consulting and Implementation Teams
- Preparing and checking provider and payroll reports
- Responding to incoming queries and managing assigned cases to resolution
- Participating in conference calls with clients and co-workers
- Ensuring appropriate procedure steps are followed